

Deep Ganatra

Student

Email ganatradeep9@gmail.com

Address 7/A, Nilgagan Appt., Diwalibaug, Athwaga

te, Surat

Phone 9429267032

Date of birth Sep 21, 2002

Nationality Indian

Link https://www.linkedin.com/in/deep-ganat

ra-a7822629a/

OBJECTIVE

Talented, motivated and experienced web developer with a good grounding in fundamental PHP, .Net Core, Java and NodeJs. It has also shown practical experience of creating Custom ORM in PHP, working on creating custom packages for mailing and JWT, and handling live projects. Skilled in working with the multiteam collaboration to develop progressive web applications. Desiring the chance to make such contributions to a progressive organization in which I can affiliate my technical capacities, ingenious problem- solving aptitude and passion for construction to reinforce effective endeavors and champion sustainable progress.

EXPERIENCE

Surat, Gujarat Oct 2022 -Apr 2024

Jr. PHP Developer

M-Square Technologies

- Collaborated with team to troubleshoot and optimize code for performance and scalability.
- Experienced with MySQL database design, optimization, and query writing for efficient data retrieval.
- Developed and maintained PHP websites and applications for clients using PHP and its Framework Laravel.
- Designed and implemented RESTful APIs for a web application using Node.js.
- Optimized server-side performance by writing efficient Node.js code.

Surat,Gujarat Dec 2023 - Feb 2024

Freelance Developer

Freelance Web Panel Development:

- Designed and developed a user-friendly admin web panel for shop management.
- Implemented functionalities for product inventory management, order tracking, and customer management.
- Integrated secure authentication and authorization for different admin roles.

Freelance Web Panel Development:

- Created an intuitive Android app for end-users to browse and customize products.
- Implemented a masking feature to allow users to visualize and personalize gifts.
- Ensured seamless communication between the web panel and the app through a robust API.

EDUCATION

Udhna Magdalla, Surat 2023 -

Present

Msc ICT

J.P.Dawar

Athwagate, Surat 2018 - 2020 H.S.C

Citizen

SKILLS

Frameworks: .Net Core 6, .Net Core MVC

•Front-End: HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, ReactJS

•Back-End: C#.Net, PHP, NodeJS, Java EE

•Web Tools/Software's/Editors - Visual-Studio, Visual Studio Code, Notepad++, GitHub

Database: Mysql, MSSQL, SQl Workbench, SQLite

Bharthana, Surat

2020 - 2023

B.C.A

C.B.Patel Computer College

1st Rank in WebIT Inter collage Competition (at Sutex Computer College) (01/2023)

1st Rank in NetRishing Inter collage Competition (at S.V.Patel Computer College) (01/2023)

Umra, Surat

2008 - 2018

S.S.C

Umrigar School

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Hindi Advanced

Gujarati Native

PROJECTS

- 1. Employee Timing System: Created an employee logging system where any company can manage their employee's timing by punch in, punch out system where upon registration of employee, an id card of employee will be generated and an web page is available for all the company where the page will access the web cam or mobile cam, can will scan the QR code on employee's id card and punch in or punch out will be marked automatically.
- 2. Moneyplant Fintech: I have solely worked on the Moneyplant Fintech, a company's project where the client, runs facebook ads for their landing pages and the data for the facebook ads would be fetched directly using cron job and this data is then filter out and send to lending partner like Bajaj, Axis, LandingKart, etc. Also there is panel available for affiliate marketer who can punch leads thorugh their panel.
- 3. HMe Gifting Shop: Have worked on this project as a freelancer where the client's requirement was to provide a web panel where he can add products(with mask for customisation), category, etc and there would be a mobile app for user where the user can order products by customising the product by adding their own images upon the masks.
- 4. PHP Packages: Have created some packages in PHP like Custom ORM, Mailing, JWT.